[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Starsky  Hutch, Ben Stiller was behind the wheel of what model and make car?", "correct_answer": "Ford Grand Torino", "incorrect_answers": ["Ford Expedition", "Pontiac Trans Am", "Dodge Charger"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This fruit is generally considered to grow on a tree, but the tree is actually a giant herb. The fruit contains potassium and vitamin B, which are necessary for the production of sex hormones.", "correct_answer": "Banana", "incorrect_answers": ["Strawberry", "Peach", "Cherry"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The movie A Clockwork Orange was set  in Scotland in the year 2005, as imagined in 1965.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the 2006 movie Cars, what was the name of the town that was the home of Mater, Luigi, Guido, Flo, Ramone, Doc and Sally?", "correct_answer": "Radiator Springs", "incorrect_answers": ["Engine City", "Transmission County", "Carborator Bottom"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "On what continent can aardvarks be found?", "correct_answer": "Africa", "incorrect_answers": ["Asia", "South America", "Australia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "People suffering from what disease should not consume raw pineapples?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Liver disease", "Ehlers-Danlos syndrome", "Hemophilia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A young goat is called a kid.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Birmingham is the most populous city of which country or US state?", "correct_answer": "Alabama", "incorrect_answers": ["Austria", "the UK", "Utah"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What High School Musical character was the head of the science club?", "correct_answer": "Taylor", "incorrect_answers": ["Sharpay", "Ryan", "Chad"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the normal life span of a platypus in the wild?", "correct_answer": "Up to 11 years", "incorrect_answers": ["Up to 22 years", "Around 2 years", "About 4 years"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of dog did Richard Nixon receive from a Texan while he was a candidate for Vice President?", "correct_answer": "Cocker Spaniel", "incorrect_answers": ["German Shepherd", "Golden Retriever", "Welsh Corgy"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This strategic board game, which involves play by two parties on an eight-by-eight square grid, enjoys a great following in Japan, and has an estimated 10 to the power of 28 legal positions.", "correct_answer": "Othello", "incorrect_answers": ["Hex", "Fanorona", "Checkers"]}]